Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Yearbooks MC.304
New York University Archives
- School of Medicine (RG 23), 1922-2012
  - The Medical Violet, 1982
    - User Copy, 1982 (Item 248)
  - The Medical Violet, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 249)
  - The Medical Violet, 1984
    - User Copy, 1984 (Item 250)
  - The Medical Violet, 1985
    - User Copy, 1985 (Item 251)
  - The Medical Violet, 1986
    - User Copy, 1986 (Item 252)
  - The Medical Violet, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 401)
  - The Medical Violet, 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Item 253)
  - The Medical Violet, 1989
    - User Copy, 1989 (Item 254)
  - The Medical Violet, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 255)
  - The Medical Violet, 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Item 256)
  - The Medical Violet, 1992
    - User Copy, 1992 (Item 257)
  - The Medical Violet, 1993
    - User Copy, 1993 (Item 258)
  - The Medical Violet, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Item 259)
  - The Medical Violet, 1995
    - User Copy, 1995 (Item 260)
  - The Medical Violet, 1996
    - User Copy, 1996 (Item 261)
  - The Medical Violet, 1997
    - User Copy, 1997 (Item 262)
  - The Medical Violet, 1998
    - User Copy, 1998 (Item 263)
  - The Medical Violet, 1999
    - User Copy, 1999 (Item 264)
  - The Medical Violet, 2000
    - User Copy, 2000 (Item 265)
  - The Medical Violet, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Item 266)
  - The Medical Violet, 2003
    - User Copy, 2003 (Item 267)
  - The Medical Violet, 2004
    - User Copy, 2004 (Item 268)
  - The Medical Violet, 2005
    - User Copy, 2005 (Item 269)
  - The Medical Violet, 2006
    - User Copy, 2006 (Item 270)
  - The Medical Violet, 2007
    - User Copy, 2007 (Item 271)
  - The Medical Violet, 2008
    - User Copy, 2008 (Item 272)
  - The Medical Violet, 2012
    - User Copy, 2012 (Item 273)
- The School of Engineering Evening Division (RG 24), 1939-1943
  - The Mast, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Box 1, Item 274)
  - The Mast, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 275)
  - The Mast, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 276)
  - The Mast, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 277)
- The School of Engineering Department of Meteorology (RG 24), 1943-1944
  - Synopsis (2-43), September 1943
    - User Copy, September 1943 (Item 278)
  - Synopsis (1-A), February 1944
    - User Copy, February 1944 (Item 279)
  - Synopsis (2-A), June 1944
    - User Copy, June 1944 (Item 280)
- College of Dentistry (RG 25), 1924-2010
  - The Dental Violet, 1924
    - User Copy, 1924 (Item 281)
  - The Dental Violet, 1926
    - User Copy, 1926 (Item 282)
  - The Dental Violet, 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 283)
  - The Dental Violet, 1928
    - User Copy, 1928 (Item 284)
  - The Dental Violet, 1929
    - User Copy, 1929 (Item 285)
  - The Dental Violet, 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 286)
  - The Dental Violet, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 287)
  - The Dental Violet, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 288)
  - The Dental Violet, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 289)
  - The Dental Violet, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 290)
  - The Dental Violet, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 291)
  - The Dental Violet, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Item 292)
  - The Dental Violet, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 293)
  - The Dental Violet, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 294)
  - The Dental Violet, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 295)
  - The Dental Violet, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 296)
  - The Dental Violet, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 297)
  - The Dental Violet, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 298)
  - The Dental Violet, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 301)
  - The Dental Violet, December 1943
    - User Copy, December 1943 (Item 299)
  - The Dental Violet, September 1944
    - User Copy, September 1944 (Item 300)
  - The Dental Violet, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 302)
  - The Dental Violet, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 303)
  - The Dental Violet, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 304)
  - The Dental Violet, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 305)
  - The Dental Violet, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 306)
  - The Dental Violet, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 307)
  - The Dental Violet, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 308)
  - The Dental Violet, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 309)
  - The Dental Violet, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 310)
  - The Dental Violet, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 311)
  - The Dental Violet, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 312)
  - The Dental Violet, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 591)
  - The Dental Violet, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 313)
  - The Dental Violet, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 314)
  - The Dental Violet, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 315)
  - The Dental Violet, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 316)
  - The Dental Violet, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 317)
  - The Dental Violet, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 318)
  - The Dental Violet, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 319)
  - The Dental Violet, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 320)
  - The Dental Violet, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 321)
  - The Dental Violet, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 322)
  - The Dental Violet, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 323)
  - The Dental Violet, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 324)
  - The Dental Violet, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 325)
  - The Dental Violet, 1970
    - User Copy, 1970 (Item 326)
  - The Dental Violet, 1971
    - User Copy, 1971 (Item 327)
  - The Dental Violet, 1972
    - User Copy, 1972 (Item 328)
  - The Dental Violet, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 329)
  - The Dental Violet, 1974
    - User Copy, 1974 (Item 330)
  - The Dental Violet, 1974-1975
    - User Copy, 1974-1975 (Item 331)
  - The Dental Violet, 1975
    - User Copy, 1975 (Item 332)
  - The Dental Violet, 1976
    - User Copy, 1976 (Item 333)
  - The Dental Violet, 1977
    - User Copy, 1977 (Item 334)
  - The Dental Violet, 1978
    - User Copy, 1978 (Item 335)
  - The Dental Violet, 1980
    - User Copy, 1980 (Item 336)
  - The Dental Violet, 1981
    - User Copy, 1981 (Item 337)
  - The Dental Violet, 1982
    - User Copy, 1982 (Item 338)
  - The Dental Violet, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 339)
  - The Dental Violet, 1984
    - User Copy, 1984 (Item 340)
  - The Dental Violet, 1985
    - User Copy, 1985 (Item 341)
  - The Dental Violet, 1986
    - User Copy, 1986 (Item 342)
  - The Dental Violet, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 343)
  - The Dental Violet, 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Item 344)
  - The Dental Violet, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 345)
  - The Dental Violet, 1992
    - User Copy, 1992 (Item 346)
  - The Dental Violet, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Item 347)
  - The Dental Violet, 1995
    - User Copy, 1995 (Item 348)
  - The Dental Violet, 1996
    - User Copy, 1996 (Item 349)
  - The Dental Violet, 1997
    - User Copy, 1997 (Item 350)
  - The Dental Violet, 1998
    - User Copy, 1998 (Item 351)
  - The Dental Violet, 1999
    - User Copy, 1999 (Item 352)
  - The Dental Violet, 2000
    - User Copy, 2000 (Item 353)
  - The Dental Violet, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Item 354)
  - The Dental Violet, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Item 355)
  - The Dental Violet, 2003
    - User Copy, 2003 (Item 356)
  - The Dental Violet, 2004
    - User Copy, 2004 (Item 357)
  - The Dental Violet, 2005
    - User Copy, 2005 (Item 358)
  - The Dental Violet, 2006
    - User Copy, 2006 (Item 359)
  - The Dental Violet, 2007
    - User Copy, 2007 (Item 360)
  - The Dental Violet, 2008
    - User Copy, 2008 (Item 361)
  - The Dental Violet, 2009
    - User Copy, 2009 (Item 362)
  - The Dental Violet, 2010
    - User Copy, 2010 (Item 363)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26), 1929-2000
  - The Prometheus, 1929
    - User Copy, 1929 (Item 364)
  - The Education Violet, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 365)
  - The Education Violet, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 366)
  - The Education Violet, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 367)
  - The Education Violet, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 368)
  - The Education Violet, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 369)
  - The Education Violet (The Seniorama), 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Box 1, Item 370)
  - The Education Violet, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 371)
  - The Education Violet, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 592)
  - The Education Violet, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 372)
  - The Education Violet, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 373)
  - The Education Violet, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 374)
  - The Education Violet, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 375)
  - The Education Violet, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 376)
  - The Education Violet, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Item 377)
  - The Education Violet, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 378)
  - The Education Violet, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 379)
  - The Education Violet, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 380)
  - The Education Violet, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 381)
  - The Education Violet, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 382)
  - The Education Violet, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 383)
  - The Education Violet, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 384)
  - The Education Violet, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 385)
  - The Education Violet, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 386)
  - The Education Violet, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 387)
  - The Education Violet, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 388)
  - The Education Violet, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 389)
  - The Education Violet, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 390)
  - The Education Violet, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 391)
  - The Education Violet, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 392)
  - The Education Violet, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 393)
  - The Education Violet, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 394)
  - The Education Violet, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 593)
  - The Education Violet, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 395)
  - The Education Violet, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 396)
  - The Education Violet, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 397)
  - The Education Violet, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 400)
  - The Education Violet, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 402)
  - The Education Violet, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 403)
  - The Education Violet, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 404)
  - The Education Violet, 1970
    - User Copy, 1970 (Item 405)
  - The Education Violet, 1971
    - User Copy, 1971 (Item 406)
  - Education Violet Review (Telos), 1972
    - User Copy, 1972 (Item 594)
  - Education Violet Review, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 407)
  - Education Violet Review, 1974
    - User Copy, 1974 (Item 408)
  - SEHNAP Violet, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 409)
  - SEHNAP Violet, 1992
    - User Copy, 1992 (Item 410)
  - SEHNAP Violet, 1993
    - User Copy, 1993 (Item 411)
  - The Education Violet, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Item 412)
  - The Education Violet, 1995
    - User Copy, 1995 (Item 413)
  - The Education Violet, 1996
    - User Copy, 1996 (Item 414)
  - The Education Violet, 1997
    - User Copy, 1997 (Item 415)
  - The Education Violet, 2000
    - User Copy, 2000 (Item 416)
  - Summer School Album, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Box 2, Item 418)
  - Summer School Album, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Box 2, Item 419)
  - Summer Session Album, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Box 2, Item 420)
  - Summer Session Album, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Box 2, Item 421)
  - Summer Session Album, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Box 2, Item 422)
  - Summer Session Album, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 423)
  - Summer Session Album, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 424)
  - Summer Session Album, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 425)
  - Summer Session Album, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 426)
  - Summer Session Album, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 427)
  - Summer Session Album, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 428)
  - Summer Session Album, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Box 2, Item 429)
  - Summer Session Album, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Box 2, Item 430)
  - Summer Session Album, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Box 2, Item 431)
  - Summer Session Album, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Box 2, Item 432)
- Higher Education Opportunity Program (RG 26.9), 1981-1985
  - Phoenix, 1981
    - User Copy, 1981 (Item 433)
  - Phoenix, 1985
    - User Copy, 1985 (Item 434)
- Stern School of Business [Undergraduate] (RG 27), 1907-2009
  - The Commerce Violet, 1907
    Produced by the Class of 1908 for the Class of 1907
    - User Copy, 1907 (Item 435)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1908
    - User Copy, May 1908 (Item 436)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1909
    Produced by the Class of 1910 for the Class of 1909
    - User Copy, May 1909 (Item 437)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1910
    - User Copy, May 1910 (Item 438)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1911
    - User Copy, May 1911 (Item 439)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1912
    Produced by the Class of 1913 for the Class of 1912
    - User Copy, May 1912 (Item 440)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1913
    - User Copy, May 1913 (Item 441)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1914
    - User Copy, May 1914 (Item 442)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1915
    - User Copy, May 1915 (Item 443)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1916
    - User Copy, May 1916 (Item 444)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1917
    - User Copy, May 1917 (Item 445)
  - The Senior War Annual, 1918
    - User Copy, 1918 (Box 2, Item 446)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1919
    - User Copy, May 1919 (Item 447)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1920
    - User Copy, May 1920 (Item 448)
  - The Commerce Violet, May 1921
    - User Copy, May 1921 (Item 449)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1923
    - User Copy, 1923 (Item 450)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1924
    - User Copy, 1924 (Item 451)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1925
    - User Copy, 1925 (Item 452)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1926
    - User Copy, 1926 (Item 453)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 454)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1928
    - User Copy, 1928 (Item 455)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1929
    - User Copy, 1929 (Item 456)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 457)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 458)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 459)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 460)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 461)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 462)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Item 463)
  - Violet News -- Special Pre-Publication Issue for the 1937 Yearbook, May 10, 1937 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 16)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 464)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 465)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 466)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 467)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 468)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 469)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 470)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Item 471)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 472)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 473)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 474)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 475)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 476)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 477)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 478)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 479)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 480)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 481)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 482)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 483)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 484)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 485)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 486)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 487)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 488)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 489)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 490)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 491)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 492)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 493)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 494)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 495)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 496)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1970
    - User Copy, 1970 (Item 497)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1971
    - User Copy, 1971 (Item 498)
  - The Commerce Violet, 1972
    - User Copy, 1972 (Item 499)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 500)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1974
    - User Copy, 1974 (Item 501)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1975
    - User Copy, 1975 (Item 502)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1976
    - User Copy, 1976 (Item 503)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1977
    - User Copy, 1977 (Item 504)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1978
    - User Copy, 1978 (Item 505)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1979
    - User Copy, 1979 (Item 506)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1980
    - User Copy, 1980 (Item 507)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1981
    - User Copy, 1981 (Item 508)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1982
    - User Copy, 1982 (Item 509)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 510)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1984
    - User Copy, 1984 (Item 511)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1985
    - User Copy, 1985 (Item 512)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1986
    - User Copy, 1986 (Item 513)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 514)
  - The B.P.A. Violet, 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Item 515)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1989
    - User Copy, 1989 (Item 516)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 517)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Item 518)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1992
    - User Copy, 1992 (Item 519)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1993
    - User Copy, 1993 (Item 520)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Item 521)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1995
    - User Copy, 1995 (Item 522)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1996
    - User Copy, 1996 (Item 523)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1997
    - User Copy, 1997 (Item 524)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1998
    - User Copy, 1998 (Item 525)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 1999
    - User Copy, 1999 (Item 526)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2000
    - User Copy, 2000 (Item 527)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Item 528)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Item 529)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2003
    - User Copy, 2003 (Item 530)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2004
    - User Copy, 2004 (Item 531)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2005
    - User Copy, 2005 (Item 532)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2006
    - User Copy, 2006 (Item 533)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2007
    - User Copy, 2007 (Item 534)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2008
    - User Copy, 2008 (Item 535)
  - Stern School of Business Violet, 2009
    - User Copy, 2009 (Item 536)
- Stern School of Business [Graduate] (RG 28), 1988-2006
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Box 2, Item 537)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1989
    - User Copy, Spring 1989 (Box 2, Item 538)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1989
    - User Copy, Fall 1989 (Box 2, Item 539)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Box 2, Item 540)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Box 2, Item 541)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Box 2, Item 542)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Box 2, Item 543)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1992
    - User Copy, Spring 1992 (Box 2, Item 544)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1992
    - User Copy, Fall 1992 (Box 2, Item 545)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1993
    - User Copy, Spring 1993 (Box 2, Item 546)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1994
    - User Copy, Spring 1994 (Box 2, Item 547)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1994
    - User Copy, Fall 1994 (Box 2, Item 548)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Spring 1995
    - User Copy, Spring 1995 (Box 2, Item 549)
  - Stern MBA Student Photo Directory, Fall 1995
    - User Copy, Fall 1995 (Box 2, Item 550)
  - Stern MBA Student Picture Book, Fall 1996
    - User Copy, Fall 1996 (Box 2, Item 551)
  - Stern MBA Student Picture Book, Fall 1997
    - User Copy, Fall 1997 (Box 3, Item 552)
  - Stern MBA Student Picture Book, Fall 1998
    - User Copy, Fall 1998 (Box 3, Item 553)
  - Stern MBA Student Picture Book, Fall 1999
    - User Copy, Fall 1999 (Box 3, Item 554)
  - Stern Full-Time MBA Student Picture Book, Class of 2001 and 2002, 2001-2002
    - User Copy, 2001, 2002 (Box 3, Item 555)
  - Stern Full-Time MBA Student Picture Book, Class of 2002 and 2003, 2002-2003
    - User Copy, 2002, 2003 (Box 3, Item 556)
  - Stern Full-Time MBA Student Picture Book, Class of 2003 and 2004, 2003-2004
    - User Copy, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Item 557)
  - Stern Full-Time MBA Student Picture Book, Class of 2004 and 2005, 2004-2005
    - User Copy, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Item 558)
  - Stern Full-Time MBA Student Picture Book, Class of 2005 and 2006, 2005-2006
    - User Copy, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Item 559)
  - Executive MBA Program in Finance Yearbook, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Box 3, Item 560)
  - Executive MBA Program Yearbook, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Box 3, Item 561)
  - Executive MBA Program in Finance Yearbook, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Box 3, Item 562)
  - Executive MBA Program Yearbook, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Box 3, Item 563)
- The School of Retailing (RG 30), 1947-1955
  - The June Clearance, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 564)
  - The June Clearance, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 565)
  - The June Clearance, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Box 3, Item 566)
  - The Annual Report, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Box 3, Item 567)
- School of Architecture and Allied Arts (RG 31), 1933-1939
  - The Pantheon, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Box 3, Item 571)
  - The Year Book, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 568)
  - The Year Book, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 569)
  - The Year Book, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 570)
- Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service (RG 33), 1974-1980
  - Yearbook, 1974-1975
    - User Copy, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Item 572)
  - Yearbook, 1975-1976
    - User Copy, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Item 573)
  - Yearbook, 1976-1977
    - User Copy, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Item 574)
  - Yearbook, 1977-1978
    - User Copy, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Item 575)
  - Yearbook, 1978-1979
    - User Copy, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Item 576)
  - Yearbook, 1979-1980
    - User Copy, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Item 577)
- Tisch School of the Arts (RG 35), 1982-2002
  - Visions, 1982
    - User Copy, 1982 (Item 578)
  - Visions, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 579)
  - Visions, 1984
    - User Copy, 1984 (Item 580)
  - "721" Tisch Senior Book, 1989
    - User Copy, 1989 (Item 581)
  - "Meet Me At 721" Yearbook, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 582)
  - The Freshman Record, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Item 583)
- Beta Alpha Psi Fraternity (RG 38.186), 1983
  - Yearbook, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 584)